Thank you for watching
Th
th
ni
shikaraba stones
dee
yes yes yes
Seino yo 2023
Please announce today's plan, Mr. Himura.
Tomisaka Demon Year-End Party
For the members who worked hard in 2023
We've set up a year-end party for the members who have worked hard in 2023!
While peeking into the atmosphere of too much freedom only for the members of the same class
We'll close out the year!
We've already shot the video, haven't we?
This will be the last broadcast of the year.
I see... This is the last one.
That was quick.
First of all, we're going to start the fourth season.
I'm really nervous.
I'm not sure I can do it.
They said it's a bad year-end party.
Everyone laughed so hard.
I don't know if it was that exciting.
Not one bit of it was exciting.
And that's the way it is.
And times like that.
After it's really over, we're all together.
Mr. Staff, where are you going to edit this?
Oh, man.
Like, "Oh, my God, where's the crew?
It's so loud.
Oh, my God.
Christmas.
Christmas. Christmas.
Sheechi and Karin
It's true, isn't it?
Let's sit down for one.
Oh, my God.
It's gonna work, isn't it?
I'm in. I'm in.
The 4th Generation Year-End Party!
Here we go.
That's a good one.
We started off right.
We decided on a good Golden's
Thank you for watching.
First of all, are you guys hungry?
I'm not hungry.
It's so nice, isn't it?
There's pizza, sushi, burger joints.
Maybe some Chinese.
Get the pizza first.
You're a real piece of work, you know that?
What's that, a Coke?
I don't know.
There's Calpis, too.
Kakuchan, have some Calpis.
One by one...
Look, the organizer is on the move!
Organizer
It's a black-body party!
Pizza is not enough for you?
Yes, indeed.
Sushi!
Sushi, sushi, sushi.
Let's have a toast.
Who's the host?
Ringo.
Ringo, are you there?
Thank you for coming to the big year-end party today!
Let's enjoy the day as much as we want.
I spilled it, didn't I?
I miss you.
Everyone's spilled.
What are you doing?
Cheers.
My knees are soaking.
I'm fine.
I'll take the first one.
You mean they'll know we're together?
You always say that.
End of show.
The show.
You want to go, Mr. Matsuo? Tomorrow?
I'll be waiting.
They're here.
Oh, yeah!
Welcome home.
Thank you for your hard work.
Good job, guys.
Everyone's on board.
They weren't all here yet.
It's my mom.
What do you want to drink?
They're here.
Yeah, we're here.
We did it.
Thanks for coming.
Can you open it?
Come on!
It's like a house party.
Oh, my God.
It's so grown-up.
It's like a commercial.
Oh, my God.
Please put your hands together, everyone.
Let's eat.
Bon appétit!
It's true!
Remika, cookies.
They're so thin.
Ah!
Yum!
We're having a gift exchange now!
Each 4th term student brings a gift with a budget of 5,000 yen
We will hold an event to give a big welcome to the guests.
We had a raffle to decide which member would receive a gift
to be able to receive gifts.
Yattenna!
Oh, I'm doing it!
Wait a minute.
Nao-chan is messing around.
I drank water like normal.
It was so salty!
Oh, no!
It tastes so good!
I'm so surprised.
Let me put it this way.
You put salt and pepper in the kurami tea.
I noticed.
Oh, my God.
There's black stuff in it.
First of all...
Tsutsui got a present from Hayashi...
Delightful.
Thank you very much.
It's full of money.
Oh no!
Seasonal fruits
Seasonal fruit
These are the ones the producers give you, right?
Look at that!
Coffee and a cup.
I have the same one.
Oh, my God.
This is a coffee warmer.
So stylish!
This is meat.
Put this on it.
It's going to stay warm all the time.
Oh, my God.
And the ring brought a set of the finest fish.
This is amazing!
I'm on a budget of 5,000 yen.
I'm about to bring a gift that I've thought through.
The flavors are
Delicious!
You always give us so much input at our shows.
Thank you.
White towel.
A towel and maybe a toothbrush.
Oh, wow.
You want to come stay at my place?
That's what I mean.
What do you mean?
You don't want me to come out to your house.
Oh, my God, baby.
I like it.
Hoshi Tsukimoto, too.
Hey...
Yes.
Nao Xiaolian.
Very nice!
And the present that Yakubo prepared for me is...
Oh, I'm so sorry.
You like it? Here.
Everyone write down 100 things you like about the fourth graders.
You don't know who you'll win.
Wow.
That's great. That's great.
That's great, that's great, that's great.
It says, "She doesn't take advantage of her cuteness.
Name your favorite thing about everyone in the fourth grade.
Wow, this is great.
The fourth light.
Wow, I'm so happy.
This is great.
This is the best part.
I wrote one for each of you.
Let's write 100 for everyone.
Oh, my God.
I'd love to see some of them.
I wrote one for each of you.
I wrote about five lines for everyone, and I wrote a lot of them.
Maybe even the last one.
You know, like a clean whirlpool or something.
If you don't do that, you won't be able to fill 100 pages.
But you wrote a hundred.
That's great.
Let's have sushi and move on.
Let's go to your favorite photo contest!
Yay!
Next, we'll bring in photos from our phones that match the theme.
and look back on the year 2023 with the photos!
The first one is the most delicious food in 2023.
Yunna-san
What is this?
What's this?
It's beautiful!
Asparagus.
When we went to a park in Hokkaido...
I went to the market to buy asparagus.
I brought them back to my parents' house.
These are both green and green asparagus.
Asparagus
They look like green onions.
Like leeks on a grilled chicken.
They look stupid.
Like leeks.
rock paper scissors
Onigiri!
Onigiri made by your mother.
What?
How fancy!
I've eaten all kinds of delicious food.
I really like...
I love Asahi's onigiri.
They're warm.
It's good stuff.
It's sugar-free.
The cutest thing in 2023.
I hear it's good.
Hey, Rey.
She's adorable.
Fourth graders versus fifth graders.
They did it.
Asahi took off her asparagus.
Surprisingly, who won?
They're really about the same height.
Devi's Unyan.
Devi's Unyan!
Devi's Unyan
Devi's Unyan.
Are you with me?
The same?
He's cute.
He's my junior.
I love him.
We've all been to dinner here before, right?
Oh, wow.
This one?
What's that like?
Just play a little card or something.
Pretend I'm going to the bathroom.
I'll come back in, shake my belly.
And then I'd go to the checkout on the way home.
And I'm like, "Where's the bill? Like that.
Oh!
He's cute.
Where did you learn how to do that?
I went to school.
You used to.
You've been there before.
2023.
This is the picture I love the most.
Thanks.
That's not yours!
It's not yours!
I started with a camera.
I went to the side in the middle.
That's when I got the best shot.
I was able to take the most beautiful picture.
I was able to make this one flourish.
I think about it a lot.
When you look at it really close
It's beautiful.
It's unique.
I don't know.
Penguins.
Mine.
You have a pet penguin, don't you?
I've never even had a stuffed animal before.
Tokyo Tower.
He's adorable.
The shed.
I showed it to him.
Wait a minute, guys.
There's a lot of stuff in the pictures.
Here you go.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, Ray.
This is...
This one.
That's it!
So cool!
I'm so in love with it.
The cut is
It's so cool.
Let's do it.
This is how my hair should be.
Here.
Oh, my God.
It looks good, doesn't it?
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no.
Oh, man.
So cool!
I'm in love with you so much.
I'm totally in love.
This is amazing!
What's this?
What's this picture of?
Base, base, base.
I did that on purpose.
Oh, my God.
eween
you
I said I don't care if it's a person or a thing, but they won't let me out at all
I don't have a follow-up, so they won't let me out.
I took a picture of myself too.
I'm so bad!
It's so uncool.
What did I put out there?
Are you in love with me?
You're in love?
My eyebrows are going up and up.
You need to erase your eyebrows with concealer.
It stands out.
Nose stands out
On top of having it drawn on
Like I'm in trouble.
This is amazing.
You have such beautiful skin.
It's so smooth.
Are you kidding me?
You're kidding, right?
Yes, it is.
What's there to say?
Really?
You're right, I'm scared.
Oh, my God.
It's so cool.
You mean with Sato Gei?
First and last name?
My full name.
I sent it to Mr. Frog right away.
That's great!
I want a sap taro from Mr. Sato Frog, don't I?
That's what I want, isn't it?
I don't want it!
Sato Frog
Sasugi's ears
This?
The back?
Back side, back side.
Everyone's so familiar with them.
I got "Mr. Yamaken".
Yamaken-san, you're gorgeous.
Oh, really?
That's all.
That's it.
That's a lot of stuff.
So much happened.
As usual.
So many things.
Take a look at that one over there.
Hey.
I'll take that one.
I thought it was for everyone.
After this, the legendary fourth-term students performed for the first time.
The end of the year-end party was almost over.
Here, Endo had a request for the 4th term students
It was a long time ago.
right after they joined the group.
Mai and Kakki from right after they joined the group.
It's kind of funny.
It's like Conan or something.
It's from a movie, right?
You know?
You know, the one where he does his impersonation of Conan?
Let me see it.
Look.
Show him.
It's the latest version of an archon.
If it's a favor from Saku.
If it's what Saku wants, I'll do it.
How's it going?
Saku!
Saku.
What do you mean? Fineness.
Fine.
It's true.
I'm embarrassed.
The wind is blowing.
Here we go.
Maruigi.
If you jump from here, you'd better jump off.
It'll be Endo.
Idiot!
If we jump from here...
The water will be like concrete.
He's got you. He's got you.
Kazuha.
If you tell him...
I'll kill you.
Idiot.
Asshole.
Dumbass.
It's the Gonenkai, isn't it?
It's the Ganenkai now, isn't it?
It's a memorial service.
If we can see Sakura's smile, we'll be done.
It's worth it.
I'm glad you could see it.
Now we'll have this year's MVP presentation.
We've voted in advance for who we think has done the best among the fourth graders.
We've voted in advance for who we thought did the best.
I'd like to announce the results.
Third place goes to...
Jang-jang!
Third place
Nao Yumiki
Nao? Congratulations!
That's great!
I got in too.
Really?
Because you've been so full of your Nao personality, both in the show and outside of the show.
That's for sure.
I did.
Next, Ayame.
Yumi...
Cute.
It's the best.
Yumiki is bursting with fun and
She's been in a lot of outside variety shows.
I thought it was great that she was so funny there too.
I'm glad.
Is she here? This hair.
Yes, I have it.
But you know how Nao always gets depressed?
She says, "Oh no, I couldn't do it." And everyone comforts her.
I really think it's thanks to all of you.
Heh...
I'm moved.
Next
Second place
Look at that!
Miyu Matsuo
I'm in too.
I'm in too!
You're in from Miyu Matsuo.
Thank you very much.
There were many moments when I felt that Miyu had turned all the feelings and experiences she had experienced into her own strength.
I have nothing but respect for you this year.
Saku-chan, after Andara was over, you sent a line to your manager, right?
And please don't tell Matsuo.
I know...
What's that?
That's not it.
When I saw Miyu at the Andaler, she was really good.
Yeah.
I'm a little embarrassed to tell you.
I didn't think it was right for me to tell you now.
I'm so glad.
Just tell the manager.
I'm not going to tell Miyu.
That's what I told her.
Thank you.
I will.
I'm sorry, this is a little...
I'm sorry.
Well, good luck with that.
And from Mona.
It was really cool to see you leading the members as the Under Center.
I could feel Matsuo's love and determination for the members.
I'm really happy to be in the same group with her.
That's a nice thing to say.
Thank you.
I'll work hard next year after seeing this.
Yay!
The honorable first place goes to...
Oh!
Yay!
Haruka Kuromi
Yay for apples!
I'm Kuromi.
I see.
I did too, Kuromi.
I'm in!
I was close with my juniors, and I was the only one who could do it, like Kuromi Haru Mantis, and I was in a lot of live performances.
Rika
Rika was able to be close to the members' hearts, make them laugh a lot, and be a mantis.
She used what she liked to do in her work.
Next Yutaka
Next Yuta
Mantis
Mantis.
They were all mantis.
Mantis
The mantis was active this year.
Ew.
Oh, my God.
That's too perfect.
You left out the miles.
And Matsuo said it was because you made everyone smile this year.
Thanks for putting a smile on my face.
Lovely words.
But really, Kuromi takes the initiative in getting to know his juniors, and I'm always grateful for that.
Thank you very much.
Like my own message
First place!
Congratulations!
First place.
MVP.
MVP first place.
Thank you very much.
Year-end party for 4th term students
We'll end the party with a song we all want to sing together to close the year.
All right.
Champing overflush, go, go!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go
Champion overflush is the best
Champin' overflush is the best
Over champin' flush, go!
I can't hit anywhere.
Lo wins!
Just get out and run away
I have to answer again
Something important, important, important...
Something important, something important
Something important, important, important
Jan-jan-jan-pin
Boom-boom-boom-boom-boom.
Aaah!
ah ah ah ah ah
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good
I'm glad you like it, but I'm always moving on a different axis than everyone else, so I want you to show me your own photos, which everyone else is missing
I was wondering which one it would be, but when I talked to Rei-chan about it...
Rei-chan said it was her, so I guess it's her
Sakura and Natsuki's imitation of Conan wasn't done on TV or something, was it?
It was popular at the end of rehearsals when we had just joined the group, and there was a video of me doing it.
So you just wanted to see the video again that you had already shown me privately? That's right.
I'm amazed you were able to do it with such quality. We had a meeting.
That was a big year-end party... that kind of performance, a year-end party.
Good night.
Thank you for watching.
Next stop.
Kindness is Love
Next preview
Even if you catch up with them and make it in time...
What are you going to say to him?
Yes, I've been wrong about you all day
A long time ago
I love you.
Thank you for watching.
I was wrong.
I'm alone.
I'm just tired, that's all.
You're nice to everyone.
I'm mad at you
Love is my story
A tale of unrequited love
And that heart
A sign that can hide it
Always monofolies
Now accepting playguide selections for Under Live
Hello, this is Tsutsui Ayume.
How was it?
I'd like to have a year-end party or something with everyone again, everyone from the third term students to the fifth term students.
I'd like to have a year-end party or something.
Please subscribe to our channel!
Bye bye!